有些同我合作的人
Someone I've been working with
他们对合约有些误解
has misunderstood their obligations to me.
预计什么时候？
24小时查询账户
未收到付款
慕尼黑的375万欧元仍未支付
去你
妈的
还有笔交易仍在酝酿之中
There's another deal brewing.
为什么你还在慕尼黑 有什么遗留问题
'Why are you still in Munich? Have you loose ends to tie up?'
埃利亚斯·费斯特
去你丫的
Fuck you.
你也需要一个代号
We'll need a codename for you.
豺狼怎么样
Why not the Jackal?
怎么了
我把查尔斯送到机场
之后我在花市看见他坐着出租车
我可以把你女儿弄出来
I can get your daughter out of prison.
把诺曼的手机号码给我 其余的事交给我处理
Just get me Norman's phone number and I'll do the rest.
我急需定位一部手机
I need a priority location on a phone.
操
Fuck!
这位是卡弗先生 他负责为我们善后
This is Mr Carver. He cleans up messes for us.
我今早和麻雀刚通过话 她已经上钩了
I spoke to Sparrow this morning. She's on the hook.
你跟她说她女儿已经死了吗
Did you tell her that her daughter's dead?
豺狼的日子
第一季 第三集
下一站是 伦敦利物浦大街
'We are now approaching London Liverpool Street
列车即将到达终点站
where this train terminates.'
伦敦  英国
你在诺曼的手机里找到什么了吗
Did you get anything from Norman's phone?
没 数据被远程清空了 但可能还有痕迹
No, it's been wiped remotely. But there'll probably be some residue.
帕迪 这很急
Paddy, this one's urgent.
-你在他包里找到了什么  -看看这个
- What did you get from his bag? - Might wanna take a look at this.
比安卡 你会喜欢的 太巧妙了
Now you're gonna love this, Bianca. It's er... very clever.
这次行动一败涂地
This operation has been a total and utter shambles from start to finish.
无辜的艾玛·斯托克
We have Emma Stoke, completely innocent,
死亡36小时 却未公布消息
whose death went unreported for more than 36 hours.
我们有两名特种部队高级特工
And we have two top Special Forces operatives
在一次拙劣的抓捕行动中丧生
killed in a botched snatch.
这一切都仅基于你对诺曼·斯托克的预感
All of it based on nothing more than a hunch you had about Norman Stoke.
必须立刻将你和这项行动都叫停
You, and this operation, need to be shut down now!
没有理由继续了 谢谢你 比安卡
I can't see a reason to keep it alive. Thank you, Bianca.
我从嫌疑人的家
I retrieved this... bag
取回了这个行李箱
from the suspect's location.
所以你找到了一个平平无奇的行李箱
So you found a bag that looks like a million other bags,
杀手恰巧用过的行李箱
one of which the assassin happened to have.
这又能证明什么呢
What does that prove?
今天早上 我带着这个箱子过海关
I took this with me through Customs this morning.
我不知道我随身携带了一把狙击步枪
I had no idea I was bringing a sniper rifle with me
安检警卫也不知道
and neither did Security.
-箱子可以拼装成狙击步枪  -太聪明了
- It's a prototype. - That is actually bloody clever.
狙击手带走了他用来杀死费斯特的武器
The sniper took the weapon he used to kill Fest with him.
像这样的
And this is how he did it.
这都多亏了诺曼·斯托克
All thanks to Norman Stoke.
-伊莎贝尔  -不行
- Isabel? - No...
情况很复杂
It's complicated.
我们刚在秘密行动中失去两位成员
We just lost two men on an op that supposedly no-one knew about.
我们得尽快搞清楚 在白俄罗斯出了什么问题
Let's get to the bottom of what went wrong in Belarus as quickly as possible.
与此同时
In the meantime...
比安卡 继续你的行动
your operation is very much alive, Bianca.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我是艾莉森 请留言
'This is Alison, leave a message.'
嗨 艾莉森 我是娜丁
Hi, Alison, it's Nadine.
实在是太抱歉
I...I can't tell you how sorry I am.
你现在必须经历的事情简直太...
What you must be going through right now is just...
我知道我现在是你最不想谈话的人
Look, I know I'm the last person you wanna speak to right now.
但是我在做一些对我意义重大的调查
But I've been doing some digging and it would mean a lot to me
我和你面对面坐下
if you'd allow me to sit down with you face-to-face,
我才能向你解释发生了什么
so I can explain what happened
并且 试着弄清这一切
and... try and make some sense of all of this.
这是你应得的
You deserve that.
再一次 我很抱歉
Again, I'm... so sorry.
好吧 收到留言请回拨 谢谢
OK, er... call me back when you get this. Thanks.
说的不错
That was very good.
我去赫勒福德 看看他们有没有列好名单
Well, I'm off to Hereford, see if they've got any names for us.
怎么现在才去
Why hasn't that been done already?
慕尼黑  德国
鲍尔先生
噢
Oh!
非常抱歉 让你久等了
我刚才在开会 去我办公室吧
方便吗
当然
谢谢
这边请
慢慢说 鲍尔先生
母亲生前没有打算
她根本没提她想要什么
现在她离我而去 让我在大房子里和两条狗为伴
我不知从何说起
你可以和我多聊聊你母亲
她总是为他人着想
她总是...
抱歉
没事
Nein.
我们专业的心理咨询帮助了很多人
我可以给你一些建议
不好意思 我可能是偏头痛犯了
不好意思 我得去车里拿药
不用 鲍尔先生
你可以把钥匙给我 告诉我车停在哪 我去给你拿药
玛赫勒女士 你真是人美心善 蓝色奥迪 药在手套箱里
我马上回来 还需要什么吗
能把窗帘合上吗 光线有点刺眼
当然
Naturlich.
远程访问安装
安装
我拿到你的药了
非常感谢
通常见效很快
别担心 鲍尔先生
不急
谢谢
不行 你还没准备好
各国媒体都会报道我父亲的葬礼
我绝不会杵着拐杖出席葬礼
报道的图像非常重要
对
但是
康复需要一段时间
我想在跑步机上走一分钟
穆勒
说说 你是如何让杀手接近我父亲的
我已经尽我所能保护他了
要真这样 他怎么会死
这样的枪击是前所未有的
费斯特先生
拜托
一分钟
我今天能坚持一分钟 你知道这意味着什么吗
明天我能坚持两分钟
远程登陆
接送车2  【司机】斯特凡·沃尔夫  【乘客】埃利亚斯·费斯特  【车牌号】MF257BUV
斯特凡·沃尔夫    车牌号 MF257BUV
加的斯  西班牙
宝贝女儿
你跟他谈过吗
妈 我当然有打电话给他
但他一出差 就不接电话
能告诉我你怎么想的吗
这不正常
你的意思是
看
嘿
Hey.
嘿 抱歉我之前没打电话
'Hey! Sorry I haven't called.'
我知道这次的交易会很复杂
I knew the deal was gonna be complicated,
但越来越荒谬
but it's got ridiculous.
一切都还好吗
'Is everything alright?'
努丽娅
Nuria?
那天我把你送到机场
The other day when I left you at the airport.
怎么了
'Yeah?'
我去了鲜花广场
I was at Plaza Las Flores...
我看见你坐出租车经过
I saw you pass in a taxi.
等等 你什么意思
Wait, what do you mean?
我看见你在出租车里 查尔斯
'I saw you in a taxi, Charles.'
好吧 我不知道你看见谁了 但肯定不是我
OK, well, I don't know who you saw but it definitely wasn't me.
我看见的就是你
But I saw you.
努丽娅 我不清楚你看见了谁 我当时真的在飞机上
Nuria, I have no idea who you saw, but I was straight on that plane.
我不知道你去哪了
I don't know where you went.
你现在在哪
Where are you now?
我现在在阿姆斯特丹的奢华酒店里
Now, I'm in an incredibly overpriced hotel in Amsterdam.
好 让我看看
OK, let me see.
-视频通话  -噢 不 求你了
- Go on video. - Oh, no, please.
你知道我讨厌视频 拜托了
You know I hate the video thing, come on.
你勾搭女人了吗
Do you have a woman with you?''
当然没有勾搭女人
Of course I don't have a woman with me.
那就让我看看你
'Then let me see you.'
努丽娅
'Nuria.'
查尔斯 让我看看你 要么我今晚来阿姆斯特丹
Charles, let me see you or I will come to Amsterdam tonight.
好吧 好吧
OK, OK. Alright, alright.
你好啊 我是你的丈夫 看 等等
Hello, it's your husband. Look, wait, wait, wait.
没有女人
No woman.
-让我看看厕所  -真的啊
- Let me see the bathroom. - Honestly?
好吧 来看看吧
OK, let's do this.
所以 这里
So... There's um...
没有化妆品 润肤乳 瓶瓶罐罐
...no make-up, no creams, no jars.
没有女人
No woman.
满足了吗
'Satisfied?'
她可能是个丑女人
She might be a very ugly woman.
是啊 我只与超级丑女有外遇
Yeah, I only have affairs with incredibly ugly women.
请让我看看儿子 可以吗
Now can I see my son, please?
妈
'Ma?'
妈 让查尔斯看看
Ma? Que vea Carlitos.
看看看 你好啊
Mira, mira, mira! Hola.
噢
Oh!
噢 你好
Oh! Que?
嗨
Hi.
你好
Que tal?
瞧瞧他 我觉得他的脸变了
Look at him, I think, I think his face has changed.
有没有
Is that possible?
你好 阿啵
Hola! A-bo!
-阿啵  -我想他了 再见 爸爸
- A-bo! - I miss him. Adios a papa.
拜拜 我爱你 拜拜
Bye-bye. I love you. Bye-bye.
我想他了
I miss him.
他也想你
'He misses you.'
我要去阿姆斯特丹
I'm coming to Amsterdam.
我很乐意
I would love that,
但我想他们应该会让我明天离开 所以
but I think they've probably got me leaving tomorrow, so...
怎么了 查尔斯 你不想让我来
What's wrong, Charles? You don't want me to come?
不 我很想你来 但是目前其实
No, I would love you to come, but I...at the moment, honestly,
努丽娅 实在是太忙乱了 我一刻也不敢放松
Nuria, it's so frenzied here that I literally don't have a minute.
我们过的这种生活不正常
This life we're living, it's not normal.
我知道不正常
Yeah, I know it's not.
你总说自己是为了工作
'You're always away. For business you say,
却对工作的事只字不提
but you never tell me anything about your business.
我从来没见过你同事
I never met any of your colleagues.'
我不知道你去做什么
I don't know what you do when you're away.
我去工作 努丽娅
'I work, Nuria.
我只是在工作 一直工作
I work, that's all I do. I just work.'
你什么时候回来
When are you coming back?
很快 就几天
Soon, a couple of days, I-
-什么时候  -我真的不知道
- 'When?' I... - Honestly, I don't know.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你永远不知道
You never know.
太令人失望了 查尔斯
It's not good enough, Charles.
伦敦  英国
极右翼为费斯特的追悼会做准备
极右翼领导人曼弗雷德·费斯特的追悼会定于今天下午在慕尼黑举行 吸引了众多媒体和政治人士的关注
你来吗
Are you coming?
亲爱的 你来吗
Love, are you coming?
他们让你来确认她的身份
They get you over here to identify her...
却连个狗屁电话都不给你打
...and then they don't even fucking call you.
呼吸点新鲜空气会让你好受些
Bit of fresh air will do you good.
你去吧
You go.
-你是谁  -你他妈以为是谁
- Who's this? - 'Who the fuck do you think it is?'
诺曼 你最近怎么样
About ye, Norman?
我很抱歉 艾玛发生了那样的事
I'm so sorry about Emma.
我无法想象你现在的感受
I can't imagine what you're going through.
是的 你不能
No, you can't.
拉里和我是来这儿带艾玛回家的
Larry and me are here to take Emma home.
你可以允许我们这样做吗
Can you not just let us do that?
你难道没有一点起码的体面吗
Do you have no common decency?
你在电话里说你在调查
You said on the phone you'd been digging?
我已经和所有人谈过了
I've spoken to everybody.
我要告诉你 没有人行为不当
And I have to tell you that no one behaved improperly.
-你知道艾玛有既往病史吗  -不知道
- Did you know that Emma had a pre-existing condition? - No.
我第一次听说 是他们打电话告诉我们消息时
First I heard of it was when they rang us to tell us the news.
这件事完全可能发生在家里 她的床上
It could just as easily have happened at home, in bed.
但是她不在床上 对吧
But she wasn't in her bed, was she?
她在拘留室 是你把她关进去的
She was in a police cell and you put her there.
我没有 艾莉森 我跟你说过
I didn't, Alison. And I've told you that.
你真的知道真相是什么吗
Do you even know what the truth is?
仔细听我说 艾莉森
Listen to me carefully, Alison.
诺曼昨天杀了两名英国军官 现在他失踪了
Norman killed two British officers yesterday and now he's disappeared.
这和我有什么关系 这与我无关
What's that got to do with me? That's nothing to do with me.
拉里的号码在诺曼的手机上 所以说
Larry's number was in Norman's phone. So...
我们当时是为了筹钱来伦敦
We were trying to get the money to go to London.
艾莉森
Alison.
协助罪犯可判十年
Assisting an offender carries a ten-year sentence.
更何况 拉里所做的一切
More, with everything Larry's been up to.
但我睁一只眼闭一只眼 因为我喜欢你
But I've turned a blind eye because I like you...
我也想帮忙
...and I want to help.
但现在你必须帮我
But now you have to help me.
你需要告诉我诺曼在哪
You need to tell me where Norman is.
滚开
Fuck off!
散步愉快吗
Did you have a nice walk?
拉里 一切都好吗
Larry, is everything alright?
你干了什么
What have you done?
什么
What?
为什么你一直让我找诺曼
Why did you keep on at me to call Norman?
我们需要钱去伦敦
We needed the money to go to London.
你知道在我给他打电话后 诺曼经历了什么吗
Do you know what happened to Norman... after I called him?
我怎么知道
How would I?
发生了什么
What happened?
他们来找他了
They came for him.
他开枪杀了几个人
He popped a couple of 'em.
他没事吧
Is he all right?
把你手机给我
Gimme your phone.
拉里 你在说什么
Larry, what are you on about?
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
娜丁是谁
Who's Nadine?
她是理发店的新员工
She's the new girl at the hairdresser's.
我现在打电话给理发店 找娜丁
So if I call the hairdresser's now and ask for Nadine...
她会接电话吗
...is Nadine gonna come on the phone?
可能吧 我不知道
She might do. I don't know.
拉里 你干嘛这样
Larry, why are you being like this?
艾莉森
Oh, Alison.
Alison.
你都干了什么啊
What have you done?
你他妈都干了些什么
What the fuck have you done?
别这样 拉里
No, don't, Larry.
不要
No!
停火
Cease fire!
站起来
Stand up!
确保枪支安全
Make safe!
谢谢各位
Thank you, gentlemen.
这些人都符合要求
These individuals all meet the parameters I was given.
你觉得 他们有谁能打出那一枪
Do you think any of these men could have made that shot?
除非他们有如神助 突飞猛进
Not unless they've improved massively from when they were here.
你确定这就是这个距离吗
Are you a hundred percent certain about the distance?
3815米
3,815 metres.
-这也太他妈远了  -德国人是这么说的
- That's a fucking long way. - That's what the Germans are saying.
没有冒犯德国人的意思
With all due respect to the Germans,
不过我建议找个人再测一下距离
I suggest someone re-measures the distance,
或者让我跟改造武器的人聊聊
or else puts me in touch with whoever modified the weapon,
不管他是谁 他懂枪
because whoever it is, he knows how to make guns.
他对我们来说很有用
We could make very good use of him here.
嗯 谢了
Yeah, well, thanks for this.
诺曼肯定知道我们要来
Norman definitely knew we were coming.
他装好了行李 准备好作战了
His bags were packed, and he was ready for a fight.
你年薪多少
What's your annual salary?
你知道我的层级 你知道我的薪资水平
You know my grade, you know the pay scales.
你丈夫不是个教授吧
And your husband, he's not a professor, is he?
他在大学教职里属于底层
He's lower down the university pecking order?
他是高级讲师 高级讲师
He's a senior lecturer. Senior lecturer?
保罗能挣多少 四五万
So, what does Paul earn? 40, 50?
这个工资还不错 不过不太高
So it's a comfortable joint wage, but not mega.
家里有钱吗
Is there family money?
-你父亲  -失踪了
- Your father was... What was he? - Missing.
-你母亲呢  -她跟诺曼·斯托克完全没关系
- And your mother? - Has nothing to do with Norman Stoke.
你也审讯过别人
You've been on this side of the table.
你知道为什么我这么问
You know why I'm asking.
你口中的我母亲 她以前是个酒鬼
My mother, if that's what you wanna call her, was an alcoholic.
现在还是
She still is.
-她现在住在福利院里  -还是你给付的钱
- She lives in sheltered housing now. - Which you pay for.
价格不菲吧
Must cost quite a penny.
你的意思是 我给诺曼·斯托克通风报信
Are you suggesting I tipped off Norman Stoke
来支付我母亲住福利院的费用吗
to pay for my mother's sheltered housing?
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money is almost always the motive.
让我跟你讲点事吧
Let me tell you something, yeah.
我为了找到诺曼 差点死了
I almost got killed trying to GET Norman.
跟我一起行动的两个人死了
Two of the men I was with are dead.
你知道我没给他通风报信 为什么还要弄出这一出闹剧
You know I didn't tip him off so why you going through this charade?
你了解我们生活的这个世界
You know the world we live in.
你不能相信任何人
You can't trust anyone.
每个人都会撒谎
Everyone lies.
谎言无处不在
About everything.
你试过查尔斯的生日吗
怎么了
不对
No.
你的呢
我的吗
不对
卡利托斯的呢
试试卡利托斯的
阿尔瓦罗 你觉得查尔斯有这么蠢吗
难说第三次会走运
不对 不可能打开
我以前用金属角磨机打开过一个保险箱 但是...
我会磨你屁股
他会发现的
听着
听我说
你有收据吗
或者购买发票
我们有了发票 就能去找制造商改密码
当然可以
这些是和翻新有关的
发票 收据 设计图 还有别的东西 看看这个
达米安 特种部队给了我一份名单
Damian? The Special Forces gave me a list
名单上有符合我们要求的狙击高手
of the best snipers who fit our parameters,
但他们觉得没人能射中那一枪
but they don't think any of them could have made that shot.
-反正查查吧  -我会的 只是...
- Well, check them out anyway. - Yeah, I will, just got to...
有查到诺曼·斯托克的什么吗
Anything on Norman Stoke?
我亲自和麻雀谈过
Er... I spoke to Sparrow in person.
有收获吗
Did you get anything?
艾玛的事让她悲愤交加
Well, she's devastated and angry about Emma.
她没心情聊
She's not in the mood to talk.
-你上次睡觉是什么时候  -我没事 真的
- When did you last get some sleep? - I'm fine, honestly.
我需要你全力以赴
I need you firing on all cylinders.
回家 歇着
Go home, get some rest.
未知来电
别人能听到我们的对话吗
'Can anyone hear us?'
你为什么打我的私人电话
Why are you calling me on my personal phone?
怎么了
What's going on?
我刚刚见过卡弗
I've just had the pleasure of Carver's company.
怎么样
How was that for you?
不怎么样 我也没有什么需要藏的事
Unpleasant, and I've got nothing to hide.
如果有人泄密 这事必须要彻查 要解决掉
But if there's a leak, it has to be investigated and resolved.
白俄罗斯发生的事肯定有点什么问题
Something definitely went wrong in Belarus.
诺曼知道我们要来
Norman knew we were coming.
我们假设一下 不是你 也不是我
Let's assume for present purposes, it's not you and it's not me.
好吧
OK.
除了我们 唯二知道这次行动的人就只有
The only other people who knew about the operation
达米安和伊莎贝尔
are Damian and Isabel.
如果是伊莎贝尔 那我们就完蛋了
Well, if it's Isabel, we're all fucked.
确实
Indeed.
-那会是达米安吗  -他为什么要这么做
- Could it be Damian? - Why would Damian do it?
他可不是个手无缚鸡之力的家伙 对吧
Not an easy fellow to pin down, is he, Damian?
他可挺有手段的
Has a sort of... slippery quality.
我们为什么来这
Why are we here?
万无一失嘛
Just to be on the safe side,
此事天知地知你知我知
what I'm going to tell you doesn't go any further.
-行吗  -行
- Agreed? - Agreed.
有个美国朋友联系了我
An American friend has been in contact.
非官方 非正式渠道
Unofficial, back channel.
我认识他二十年了
I've known him for 20 years.
安卡拉和东京的前任站长
Ex-station chief in Ankara and Tokyo.
沉着冷静 头脑清晰
Level-headed, very judicious.
美国人担心费斯特遇刺一事
The Yanks are worried that the assassination of Fest
会引发针对政客的刺杀热潮
will spark copycat murders of politicians.
他们十分希望能查明真相
They're very keen to get to the bottom of it
并且一直与我们密切联络
and had been liaising closely with us.
但现在他的部门被告知
But now his department has been told
不要与303分享任何信息
to not share any information with 303.
要么卡弗是对的
Well, either Carver's right
要么美国人想搞破坏
or the Americans are trying to sabotage us.
美国人没有提前得知我们在白俄罗斯的行动
The Americans didn't know about the Belarus operation until after it happened.
所以 如果我朋友说得没错
So... if my friend is right,
问题还是出在我们内部
the problem is in-house.
从现在起 行动尽量保密
From here on, keep the circle tight.
怎么了 亲爱的
没道理啊
什么没道理
房间
书房
衣橱
这间房是啥
这间房他妈是啥
慕尼黑  德国
-早啊  -你看过你的账户了吗
- Good morning. - 'Have you checked your account?'
我看到定金到账了 对
Er, I saw that the er, commencement fee had landed, yeah.
很好
Good.
罗丹22号会去塔林
Rodin is going to be in Tallinn on the 22nd.
你现在出发 就能有足够的时间准备
If you leave now you'll have plenty of time to prepare.
-消息可靠吗  -千真万确
- 'How reliable's that information?' - A hundred percent.
明白了 我着手安排
Understood. I will start making arrangements.
我猜你慕尼黑的事情已经完成了
And we're assuming you finished whatever business you had in Munich?
差不多吧
Well, that seems like a decent assumption.
很好 我们给了你很多钱
'Good to hear. We've paid you a lot of money
我们希望你专心干活
and we expect to have your complete attention.'
没问题
Absolutely.
打开后备箱
别开枪
进去
好的
不要
麻雀
聪明点 帮我就是在帮你自己
跟卡弗见面怎么样
How was the Carver experience?
他只是在履行自己的职责
Yeah, he was just doing his job, I suppose.
这是狙击手名单
Here's the list of snipers.
又臭又长 但这就是军方给你的
Appallingly analogue, I know. But that's the Army for you.
他们都已经退役了 汤普森在监狱里 过失杀人
And they've all left the Service. Thompson's in prison. Manslaughter.
克莱格患有多发性硬化症 我有其他人的地址
Clegg has MS. I have addresses for the others.
你想让我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
-查查费斯特遇刺时他们在哪  -收到
- Find out where they were when Fest was killed. - Copy that.
-谢谢  -麻雀那边有消息吗
- Thank you. - Anything from Sparrow?
-还没有  -比安卡
- Not yet. - Bianca.
在手机里发现了有趣的东西
Found something very interesting on the phone.
帮我带杯咖啡 好吗
Can you get me a coffee, please?
黑咖啡 不加糖
Er, black, no sugar.
谢谢
Cheers.
-你有什么消息吗  -挺难的
- Eh, what you got for me? - Well, it was tough.
这些东西加密非常复杂 可能是国家级的
There's some very serious encryptions. I'd say state level.
几乎所有数据都被远程清除
Almost all of the data's been wiped remotely.
我们只能恢复打进来和打出去的号码
And we were only able to recover incoming and outgoing numbers.
内容没有 但是
None of the content but...
在曼弗雷德·费斯特被杀前的三周里
in the three weeks leading up to Manfred Fest's murder,
有一个号码频繁联系他
there was a flurry of calls and messages from a single number.
有意思的是
Now, interestingly,
在费斯特被杀的那天 联系就终止了
they stopped completely the day Fest was murdered.
-这个联系人叫什么  -豺狼
- Did you get a name for the caller? - Yeah, well, Jackal.
-豺狼  -明显是个代号
- Jackal? - Well, it's codename, obviously.
好吧
Alright.
-好吧 你继续忙  -谢谢
- Alright, I'll leave you to it. - Cheers.
豺狼
忧伤 孤独 无助  他们生活在城市废墟中  有多种含义  有着不同颜色的鬃毛
-穆勒女士  -费斯特先生
- Frau Muller. - Herr Fest.
他从不向除我之外的人展示这一面
亲爱的
你跟你姐姐聊过了吗
我永远无法从这件事中走出来
妈妈 谢谢你关心
我的康复情况
我中枪了
中了两枪
埃利亚斯 别太自作多情
我的律师会联系你的律师 我想知道爸给了你多少钱
我要我的那份
你现在
跟我说这个
费斯特先生 备好车了
你母亲和姑母坐第一辆
你要和你姐姐坐一起吗
不
朱莉亚不能跟我一起走
你这卑鄙下流的混蛋
拿上拐杖
当然
都检查了吗 窗户 屋顶
费斯特先生 请走快一些
没事吧
需要帮助吗
我坐后面的车
继续开 跟紧
一定很疼吧
是啊
不关你的事
腿怎么样了
你是谁啊
你知道我是谁
追
费斯特先生 怎么回事
我他妈不知道
快来救我 穆勒 你在干嘛 快来救我
穆勒
Muller!
穆勒 穆勒
Muller! Muller!
会很响
你是什么人
不要
No...
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
对不起
Look. I'm... I'm sorry.
我雇你杀我父亲 然后你射伤了我
I...I hired you to shoot my father and then you shot me.
我就是 很生气
So I was just... I was mad.
就是很生气
Ah, ah, I was just mad.
求求你 从我的角度想想
See it from my point of view, please.
穆勒
我会付你钱 我发誓
I'll pay you, I promise. I promise.
你想要多少钱都行
I'll pay you... I'll pay you whatever you want.
这不是钱的事
But it's not about the money.
埃利亚斯
Elias.
去你妈的
Fuck... You.
安全警报 检测到移动
麻雀  消息
我愿意帮忙
2号摄像头 实时画面